websouls.com 2016-12-01

# Hosting in Pakistan | Web Hosting Pakistan | PK Domains | WebSouls

Use of the WebSouls websites and services indicates your consent to the collection and use of information as described below.

Any questions which you may have regarding this privacy policy should be directed to [info@websouls.com](mailto:info@websouls.com).

**1\. What information is collected and how is it used?**

We ask you to supply certain information when you use our site, especially when you sign up with us as a customer. This information will be used in the management of our own database and to enable us to contact you about the service you have requested (for example, to confirm the registration of a domain name or to inform you of the need to renew your registration when it expires). We may also use your email address to send you our regular WebSouls newsletters. If you wish you may opt out from receiving these newsletters (see "WebSouls Newsletter" below). In addition, when you use our website we may store your IP address and may use this information to administer our website and help to diagnose any network or server problems. We may use cookies to keep track of your use of our website and e-commerce system. Information passed to us from your web browser may be stored and used in our internal statistical analysis. We may also automatically collect non-personal information about you such as the type of internet browsers you use or the site from which you linked to our website. You cannot be identified from this information and it is only used to assist us in providing an effective service on our website.

**2\. Do we share the information with anyone else?**

WebSouls will not, without your consent, pass your personal information to a third party except in the following circumstances:

2.1 in order to register a domain name we are required to send certain information like your name, business name (if applicable), postal address and email address etc to organisations that formally record the registration; this information may be available to others via a "Whois" search;

2.2 if required to do so by law or by any organisation with appropriate authority;

2.3 if you have signed up for optional services which require us to pass your personal information to another company (see "Optional Services" below)

2.4 to any financial institution with whom we hold an account for the purpose of verifying credit status and / or validating financial transactions;

2.5 we may provide aggregate statistics about our sales, customers, traffic patterns and other site information to third parties, but these statistics will not include any information that could personally identify you;

2.6 in order to assist us in understanding our customer base some anonymous information (i.e not name or specific address) may from time to time be passed on to a third party for data analysis.

2.7 as part of a sale or transfer of the shares and/or assets of WebSouls Limited. WebSouls Limited is not responsible for the privacy practices of other companies or websites. 3. Credit Cards

Credit card payment for our services is processed by our secure payment service provider. We do not record your credit card details on our database and the payment service provider does not record any other information about you.

**4\. WebSouls Newsletter**

From time to time WebSouls will send newsletters to those customers who have opted to be included on our various customer mailing lists. New customers have the opportunity to decide to opt in or out of these mailing lists when they first sign up with us to create an account. Existing customers or other people who are interested in the newsletters may opt in or out by sending an email request to our support team.

**5\. Optional Services**

From time to time WebSouls may offer additional services to our customers. In some cases these services may require us to pass personal data held by us to a third party. Any such service will be optional and the offer will be to those who have opted-in at the time of sign-up or otherwise.

**6\. How long will we hold data on you?**

WebSouls will not hold data for longer than is reasonably necessary for the purposes of the proper conduct of its business or as required by law.

**7\. Where is the data we hold stored?**

Information which you submit via our website is stored on a computer and sometimes on paper at our offices. This is necessary in order to process the information and to send you any information you have requested.

**8\. Security**

WebSouls places great importance on the security of all information associated with its customers and has security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of customer data under our control. With regard to our website, we may use secure server software (SSL) to encrypt information you input before it is sent to us. While we cannot ensure or guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur, we use our best efforts to prevent this.

**9\. Links to Other Sites**

The WebSouls website contains advertising and links to other websites. No personal information is passed to other websites if you follow one of these links. WebSouls is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of linked websites. We would encourage you to read the privacy statements of other websites, since their privacy policy may differ from ours.

**10\. Changes to Personal Information**

If you need to change the information that we keep, for example because you have moved or to correct an error, please contact us.

**11\. Consent**

Use of the WebSouls.co.uk website and services indicates your consent to the collection and use of information as described in this policy. Any changes to the policy will be posted on this page.

**12\. Service Announcements**

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement, if, for instance, a service is temporarily suspended for maintenance. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account.

**12\. Your Responsibility**

You are responsible for the security of your Account Number and passwords. Make sure you keep it in a safe place and do not share it with others.

Always remember to log out after your session ends, to ensure that others cannot access your private personal information. You should take this precaution even if you are not using a public computer, such as at a library or internet café, but even when using your private computer in your home.

**12\. Governing Law**  
WebSouls Limited is a UK company and this privacy policy is intended to be interpreted under English law.
